platinumservermanagement.com 2018-12-27

# Platinum Server Management, Inc. - 24x7x365 cPanel Server Management

_Platinum Server Management, Inc._ is dedicated to protecting your privacy and handling any personal information obtained from you with care and respect. This Privacy Policy is designed to answer your questions regarding our privacy policies and principles. 

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site.

_Platinum Server Management, Inc._ is the sole owner of the information collected on www.platinumservermanagement.com. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

If you purchase a service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to verify and process your orders. We may call you to verify the order for security purposes and/or request additional security/verification information to verify and validate your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

We provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by emailing us at sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. 

Cookies:

A cookie is a small piece of data that a website stores on your device when you visit, typically containing information about the website itself, a unique identifier that allows the site to recognise your web browser when you return, additional data that serves the purpose of the cookie, and the lifespan of the cookie itself. 

We use cookies to help improve your experience of https://www.platinumservermanagement.com . This cookie policy is part of Platinum Server Management, Inc.'s privacy policy, and covers the use of cookies between your device and our site. 

If you don't wish to accept cookies from us, you should instruct your browser to refuse cookies from https://www.platinumservermanagement.com . Most browsers are configured to accept cookies by default, but you can update these settings to either refuse cookies altogether, or to notify you when a website is trying to set or update a cookie. If you browse websites from multiple devices, you may need to update your settings on each individual device. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

We set a persistent cookie to remember the affiliate you found our site through. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site. 

Log Files:

As is true of most Web sites, the web server gathers certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), country, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, device info, geolocation data, device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, device settings, etc. What we collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and software. We recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider to learn what information they make available to us. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our visitors and user base as a whole. 

Personal information 

To sign up with our service, we ask for personal information, such as your: 

Name, Email, Phone, Address, and Payment information. 

This data is considered "identifying information", as it can personally identify you. We only request personal information relevant to providing you with a service, and only use it to help provide or improve this service. You can update and/or remove this information at any time through our Client Login. Credit card information collected is submitted to our third party merchant payment processor solely for payment purposes. 

Server information 

To provide our service, we ask for your server information. This data is used to provide server management, monitoring, technical support, and related services. You can update and/or remove this information at any time through our Client Login. 

If your personally identifiable information or server information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change inside our Client Login information page or by emailing sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

The security of your personal information and server information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or server login information) on our forms it is transmitted through secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

How we collect information 

We collect information by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we're collecting it and how it will be used. You are free to refuse our request for this information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services without it. If you are unclear, unsure, or do not fully understand how information is collected and/or used, please email us to sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

If you have any questions about privacy, security, policies, procedures, or anything at all regarding our service, company, or website, you can send email us at sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name, email address, web site address only with the client's consent. 

_Platinum Server Management, Inc._ recognizes the need to provide additional protections for children under the age of thirteen who visit our sites. To further protect children, _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ does not conduct business with children under the age of thirteen. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our websites. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this web site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ "Terms of Service" (http://www.PlatinumServerManagement.com/TOS.html). Children under the age of 13 may not use this web site and parents or legal guardians may not agree to the _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ "Terms of Service" on their behalf. If you do not agree to and/or cannot comply with any of the _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ "Terms of Service", do not use this web site. As a parent/guardian, please contact us if you believe your child is participating in an activity involving personal information on our website, and you have not received a notification or request for consent. 

International customers: If you have provided information to _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ from a country other than the United States, your information may be transferred to, and processed by _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ in the United States or other countries other than your own. If you provided information from a country that grants specific additional privacy rights, contact _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ at the address below to exercise your rights. 

**Does _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ share personally identifiable information to third party marketing organizations?**   
No. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ does not sell, rent, share, or otherwise give your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. Often, companies receive extra income by providing customer contact information to marketing companies. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ does not provide customer contact information to marketing companies. For example, _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ will not give your address to junk mail ("direct marketing") companies or email marketers (including "spammers").  **Does _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ share personally identifiable information to any other third parties?**   
Not in the normal course of day-to-day business. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ does not provide your personally identifiable information to anyone, without your permission, unless compelled by law, in order to collect unpaid debts, to protect your security and safety, enforce the "Terms of Service" of _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ , or to protect the security and safety of _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ web sites, third party web sites, and _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ employees.  **What information does this Privacy Policy cover?**   
Except as specifically described below, this Privacy Policy applies only to personally identifiable information collected on the web sites where this Privacy Policy is posted and this Privacy Policy does not apply to any other information collected by _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ by any other means. This Privacy Policy applies to any use and sharing of personally identifiable information collected on or after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted. However, for customers that used our web sites and/or services before the date that this Privacy Policy was posted, _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ will apply this Privacy Policy to personally identifiable information associated with the customers only if the customer accepts the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Once accepted the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, this Privacy Policy will also apply to personally identifiable information collected from the customers before the date that this Privacy Policy is posted. 

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information", this means information that identifies a particular individual, such as an individual's name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number. 

**What types of personally identifiable information does _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ collect about customers?**   
Much of the personally identifiable information received comes directly from customers interested in obtaining various services from _Platinum Server Management, Inc._. Usually, this information includes a customer's name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ collects personal information when a customer registers, logs on, or visits _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ web sites. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ may also collect other types of information such as credit card information, the type of services ordered or purchased, and the date of the order or purchase. 

_Platinum Server Management, Inc._ also collects certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to our web sites. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ collects this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to our web sites and to prevent fraud. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. 

**How do you safeguard customer's personally identifiable information?**   
The security and confidentiality of your personally identifiable information is extremely important to _Platinum Server Management, Inc._. Technical, administrative, and physical security measures are used to protect customer information from unauthorized access and improper use. From time to time, Platinum Server Management reviews security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware that, despite best efforts, no security measures are perfect or completely impenetrable.  **How can a customer update contact information?**   
Contact information provided by you may be accessed, updated, or deleted in our Client Login or by simply sending an e-mail to sales@platinumservermanagement.com. Please provide information in the e-mail that will help _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ identify your account. _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ may also provide you with an opportunity to update your contact information by sending you an e-mail or other communication that invites your response.  **How can a customer ask questions, or send comments, regarding this Privacy Policy?**   
If you have questions or wish to send comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to sales@platinumservermanagement.com   
Please be assured that any personal information that you provide in communications to the above email and mailing addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you so request.    
  
**How does a customer know when this Privacy Policy is amended?**   
_Platinum Server Management, Inc._ may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If any material changes are made in the way that personally identifiable information or server information is collected, used and/or shared, you will be notified by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the web sites covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days followed by dispatch of an email notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days followed by posting of notice of the changes on the web sites covered by this Privacy Policy. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ with your current email address. If your last email address provided is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the above described notice, dispatch of the email containing such notice will nevertheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. Changes to this Privacy Policy may effect the use, by _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ , of personally identifiable information provided by you before being notified of the changes. If you do not wish to allow changes in the use of your information, you must notify _Platinum Server Management, Inc._ before the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with _Platinum Server Management, Inc._. 

**Use of information**

We may use a combination of identifying and non-identifying information to understand who our visitors are, how they use our services, and how we may improve their experience of our website in future. We do not disclose the specifics of this information publicly. 

We may use your personal details to contact you with updates about our website and services, follow up on previous communications, remind you about necessary updates to previously installed software, along with promotional content that we believe may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of receiving any or all notifications from us, you can notify us by email to sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

**Your rights and responsibilities**

As our user, you have the right to be informed about how your data is collected and used. You are entitled to know what data we collect about you, and how it is processed. You are entitled to correct and update any personal information about you, and to request this information be deleted. You may amend your account information at any time, using the tools provided in your account control panel. You may delete your entire account by contacting us directly by email to sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

Feel free to contact us if you have any concerns or questions about how we handle your data and personal information.   
Platinum Server Management, Inc. Data Controller  
sales@platinumservermanagement.com   
Platinum Server Management, Inc. Data Protection Officer  
sales@platinumservermanagement.com 

**Limits of our policy**

This privacy policy only covers Platinum Server Management, Inc.'s own collecting and handling of data. We only work with partners, affiliates, datacenters, service providers, contrators, and third-party providers whose privacy policies align with ours, however we cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices. 

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices. 

**Changes to this policy**

At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect current acceptable practices. An updated date stamp will be placed on our site next to the Privacy Policy link. Your continued use of this site after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. 

**Data processing and storage**

The server information and personal information we collect is stored and processed in the United States of America, or where we or our partners, contractors, employees, affiliates, datacenters, and third-party providers are located and maintain facilities. 

We only retain server information for as long as necessary to provide a service, or to improve our services in future. While we retain this data, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. That said, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, and cannot guarantee absolute data security. 

To request your personal information to be deleted, please email us to sales@platinumservermanagement.com and we will erase it from our system within a reasonable timeframe. 

Payment information is transmitted through our Third-party payment processor solely for payment processing. 

We will refuse government and law enforcement requests for data if we believe a request is too broad or unrelated to its stated purpose, however, we may cooperate if we believe the requested information is necessary and appropriate to comply with legal process, legally obligated/obligated by law, to protect our own rights and property, to protect the safety of the public and any person, to prevent a crime, or to prevent what we reasonably believe to be illegal, legally actionable, or unethical activity. 

We do not otherwise share or supply personal information to third parties. We do not sell or rent your personal information to marketers or third parties.
